heartlandamerica.com 2016-06-17

# Heartland America: Privacy Policy

Heartland America® knows that you care how information about you is used and shared, and we appreciate your trust that we will do so carefully and sensibly. By visiting Heartland America® you are accepting the practices described in this Privacy Statement.

## Registration

If you choose to register with our website you will be asked to provide contact information including your name and your email address. This information is used to contact the user about the services on our site for which they have expressed interest.

By providing your cellular phone number, you agree to receive non-telemarketing calls or text messages to that number, including calls or texts delivering messages related to your account and purchases. For efficiency, we may at times contact you using autodialed or pre-recorded calls or messages. Where we are required to obtain your consent for such calls or messages, you may opt out at any time.

## Merchandise

In order for Heartland to ship merchandise to you, you will need to provide Heartland with certain information on our order form. This information includes contact information, such as your name and address, and financial information, such as your credit card number and expiration date. This information is necessary for billing purposes and fulfilling your orders. If we have trouble processing your order, this contact information is used to get in touch with you.

## Cookies

A cookie is a piece of data stored on your computer's hard drive that identifies you as a Heartland America® user. This cookie does not contain any personal information about you.

## Credit Card Processing

Heartland America® utilizes the strength and security of major third party credit card processing companies to authorize and bill your credit card for the merchandise shipped to you. These companies do not retain, share, store or use personally identifiable information for any secondary purposes.

This web site takes significant precautions to protect confidential information. When you submit sensitive information via the website, your information is sent using the latest in encryption technology (provide by Verisign Inc.).

## Email Promotion Subscriptions

Upon placing an order through the Site, you will begin receiving the Heartlandamerica.com email newsletter, based on the Personal Information you have provided, unless you opt-out of receiving such communications. Our subscribers receive special deals, closeouts, and product liquidations. Every communication we send allows you to unsubscribe if you change your mind and decide not to receive email from us. To stop receiving promotional emails or newsletters from us by sending an email to the contact address below or by clicking here to unsubscribe.

Email: [info@heartlandamerica.com](mailto:info@heartlandamerica.com)  
Phone: 1-800-229-2901

Street Address:   
Heartland America   
Attn: Mail Preference Service   
8085 Century Boulevard   
Chaska, MN 55318

Please note that it may take up to 7 days to remove you from our email subscription list.

## Review Posting Policy

Heartland America, (and its affiliates, collectively referred to as "Heartland"), appreciates customer comments and reviews ("content"), and will periodically post such content on its websites or in other advertising. By submitting content, customer consents to the use of such content, and use of such customer"s name or initials associated with such content, without compensation and as Heartland sees fit.

Customer submitting content further grants Heartland a non-exclusive, perpetual and worldwide royalty free license for the use of such content in any and all media as Heartland sees fit. Customers submitting content further agree and understand that Heartland must exercise an appropriate amount of control over such content, and must make decisions about which content to post, and in which venues. This means that not all content will be posted, and customer shall have no recourse or say regarding whether any particular content is posted or used in any form.

Content that is considered off topic will be deemed inappropriate and will not be posted. Likewise, content that exhibits offensive, inappropriate, threatening or obscene language or rhetoric, or contains misrepresentations of fact, will be deemed inappropriate and therefore also will not be posted.

Heartland reserves the right to post, not post, edit or delete content that is submitted through this website or those of its affiliates. Heartland assumes no liability for any content posted, or submitted but not posted, to or stored within any of its websites and databases.

While Heartland makes every effort to review and screen all content submitted by its customers, given the sheer volume of content it is not always possible to do so. Heartland assumes no liability for inadvertently posting content that may violate its stated posting policy, nor for any failure to review or post any particular submitted content.

## Correcting/Updating Personal Information

If you need to change any of the personal information that you have previously provided us, please go to [My Account](https://www.heartlandamerica.com/customer/account/) or send an email to our Customer Support department.

## Mailing list preference

Occasionally we make our mailing list available to carefully screened companies whose products or services might interest you. If you'd prefer to have your name withheld, please send your mailing label to: Heartland America, Mail Preference Service, 8085 Century Boulevard, Chaska, MN 55318-3056

## Notification of Changes

Anytime Heartland America® changes its privacy statement, we will post it on our web site.
